Thank you all so much for coming
十分感谢各位的光临
And for helping us raise enough money to... save Camp Everfree!
帮助我们筹到足够的钱去...拯救森灵营地
Thank you For everything
谢谢你们所做的一切
Oh, if I'd just asked for help in the first place...
要是我一开始就向你们求助就好了
Heh, don't sweat it, it's kinda what we do
哈，小菜一碟，这是我们应该做的
Not to brag or anything
不是我吹嘘
but it's pretty cool how I saved all those campers from those Rubus fruticosus
但我从那些Rubus fruticosus里救出所有露营者时的身姿真的非常酷
Blackberry brambles
黑莓荆棘
I'm familiar with the genus
我对这种植物很熟悉
it's just a little weird you say you saved the campers
只是你说是你救了那些露营者有点奇怪
I thought I saved them
我以为是我救了他们
Yeah
没错
But I saved you from falling on the docks
但我救了你，没有让你跌到码头上
so that you can save the campers
这样你才能救下那些露营者
So technically, it was all me
所以严格来讲，这都是我的功劳
I'm really glad I met you
我很高兴能遇见你
Uh-oh
呃
What?
怎么？
That sounds like a goodbye
那听上去是告别了
And here I was hoping we'd still be able to hang out
我还想和你约个会来着
Maybe get dinner and catch a movie?
比如一起吃个饭看个电影
Yeah. I'd really like that
嗯，我很期待
Oh, good!
哦，好极了
I was hoping that's what this meant
那看来不是再见了呢
Oh, uh, sorry
噢，呃，抱歉
I need to borrow Timber
我得拉走一下云杉
There are some donors I really want him to meet
我真的需要让他去见见一些捐赠者
They were good friends with mom and dad
他们都曾是爸爸妈妈的好友
Save me a dance, okay?
给我留一支舞，好吗
Uh-huh
呃 好
Adorable
太可爱了
He does seem like a pretty cool guy
他看上去确实是个很酷的家伙
You know what else is cool?
你们知道还有什么特别酷吗？
Our awesome new superpowers!
我们超棒的超能力！
I handed out, like, four hundred fliers
我发了大概，四百张传单
set up the stage
搭建起舞台
and still had time to pick up pizza
然后仍然能抽时间拿上披萨
I love my superspeed!
我爱我的超级速度！
About that
关于这个
I think the crystals are the source of the superpowers
我想这些水晶就是超能力的来源
You're not gonna ask us to give them up, are you?
你没有想要我们放弃它们吧？
No
不
In fact, I think maybe we were meant to have them all along?
事实上，我想也许我们本来就该拥有它们？
Me too
我也是
There is one thing I'm still wondering about, though
不过有一件事我还是很想知道
What's that?
是什么？
Where did the magic that hit this cave come from?
飞进洞穴的魔法到底是从哪儿来的？